Don't chase too far! Yuliy!
Where is he?
He's going to get swept away! Grab a light!
Are you all right?
Daddy! He woke up! Daddy!
If I'm to live
by inertia
There's probably nothing
wrong with giving up
But I don't want the night stolen from me
The moon shines down on me as if to comfort my shuttered heart
I'm left with only a cold blade
I'm just losing myself
I'm searching
Just like this planet that's lost everything
I don't think that I'm always right
But I'm not going to regret what I do now
Making just one wish, I fade into the night
There you go.
Thank you very much.
I should mention that, with the way that I found you,
I thought it best to report what happened to the police.
Don't hold it against me.
Of course.
I must say you're remarkably vigorous.
And he was really hungry, too!
He was asleep for two whole days, after all.
Um...
My name is Harada Kisuke.
Are you a doctor?
More or less.
This is my daughter, Saki.
It's nice to meet you!
My name's Yuliy.
Yuliy?
Are you from overseas?
Yes, although—
How come you can speak Japanese?
Why are your eyes not dark?
And why is some of your hair white?
Well...
That's too many questions, Saki.
Why don't you clear those dishes away?
Okay!
Now, I have to get back to my work.
Excuse me.
You have guests, sir.
She's pretty suspicious of us.
Are you sure she's not just scared of your face?
You think it's me?
I told you not to chase too far.
I couldn't stop myself.
I could feel the animal blood rushing though my veins.
An animal wouldn't cast its bond with the pack aside like that.
Especially not a wolf.
I had a dream.
A dream of back then.
If I had resisted the animal blood back then,
you wouldn't have been able to save me.
I would just have been dead.
It is true that your animal blood is of great aid to you.
However, you must not allow yourself to drown in it.
The moment you do, you'll no longer be a Jaeger.
I understand.
I've talked to the master of this house.
He says you can stay until you're healed.
I'm healed enough.
If I just keep the bandages tight—
Just accept the man's kindness.
Philip will stay here with you, just in case.
Why me? Why not Fallon?
Well you see, it seems that I'm too scary for the little girl.
Take good care of him.
Hey, hands off my hair!
This is the police!
Don't move!
Yuliy...
Can't sleep?
Where's your dad?
He's working.
I'm not supposed to disturb him.
What about your mom?
She's in Heaven.
All right.
I'll read a book for you until you get sleepy.
Thanks for being my big brother tonight, Yuliy!
Your big brother, huh.
Collection of Japanese Fairy Tales
Worldwide Anthology
of Boys' and Girls' Literature
Did your mom get sick?
Worldwide Anthology
of Boys' and Girls' Literature
Yeah.
Daddy was so sad. He kept crying that even though he was a doctor, he couldn't save her.
Your dad works pretty late.
Yeah.
He said he's making something so great that he can't sleep.
Something great?
He said it would make Mommy happy, too!
Well, I hope he finishes soon, then.
Me too!
Go ahead and report.
The culprits broke into the residence of the biologist Abe Yoshiyo and, after murdering him,
engaged and killed several of the officers who arrived to investigate.
The Hyakko Party, then?
Yes.
That group's got a long list of targets.
They kill new money and old money families... public and private
researchers... all while wearing those strange masks.
Their leader, Momose Naotora, calls himself the last true samurai,
and demands the revival of the feudal system and equality for—
"Terrorists."
Terrorists?
That's what groups like that are called in France.
The reason they can move in such numbers and not get caught is likely that they have a strong backer.
Then that's the source of their funding.
I'm guessing that it's a foreign intelligence agency.
But they call for the expulsion of foreigners.
It's hardly uncommon for someone not to mean what they say.
Then you think it's V Shipping?
They were the ones who turned the streets into a warzone the other day.
I'm not sure yet.
Whatever we do, we mustn't misjudge the font of all this chaos.
That said, people like them must not be allowed to walk around our capital like they own the place.
That is where we come in.
Welcome.
Make me a mockingbird with lemon instead of lime.
I'm very sorry, but we're out of lemon right—
Are you sure you don't have one in the back?
I never expected a day to come when I'd have to actually use that countersign.
Alma Company.
You know of them?
They're our competitors.
In our official line of work, that is.
They recently started doing business with the military here.
They've been selling and developing weapons.
That's much more brazen than I'd expect.
You think that Kershner's group is involved?
I'd expect them to act more cleverly than this, though.
I'll continue to gather information.
Big brother got better!
His body sure is crazy.
He was treated by Doctor Harada, after all.
He's always been an excellent surgeon.
Heart surgery was his specialty.
Oh, yeah?
So he took it very hard when his wife died of a heart condition.
He stopped practicing to spend his time developing a new medical device.
By himself?
He used to have an assistant,
but they've been missing since the other day.
Oh, I apologize. I shouldn't make you listen to all this blather.
Please enjoy your stay.
They sure are getting along.
These are going to need supports.
Do you mind if I make some?
No, that would be great!
Mommy was the one who decided to grow tomatoes!
She said that Daddy's always busy with work,
so we should make something nutritious to give him!
Your mom sounds kind.
Is your mommy kind too?
She was.
She's gone now, though.
She's up in Heaven?
I bet they're friends up in Heaven, just like us!
Yeah.
I'm sure they're watching over us together.
In fact, my mother whispers to my heart.
Your heart?
Yep.
"I know you can do it," she tells me.
I can't shut my ears to the words of the dead.
Father!
I heard Yuliy was hurt!
Ryouko!
Knock before you enter a room!
I'm— I'm very sorry!
He's not in any mortal danger.
There's no need to worry.
Oh, thank goodness.
Would it be possible for me to pay a visit—
Thank you for your concern,
but he'll be back in only a few days.
But—
Ryouko.
Acting without thought causes trouble for others.
Restrain yourself.
Thank you for the lesson.
You seem to be letting your mind wander.
Sensei, I'd like to have one more match.
Oh? That's fine with me.
There's something I'd like to ask of you should I win.
Anything for you, Miss Ryouko.
In that case, if I'm victorious, I'd like you to tell me where Yuliy is staying.
Miss Ryouko, th—
I'm ready to begin!
I seem to have lost a round
before we even begin.
Do you think the Hyakko Party could be ninjas?
I mean, they're masked and wear all black.
And then there's the stuff they write in blood on the wall.
I bet those are some kind of ninja spells!
"Divine Retribution."
"Punishment" might be a better translation.
But that doesn't make sense.
The man they killed last night was a biologist.
"Punishment" for a scholar?
You're right, that does seem strange.
I'll need to investigate whether there have been any similar cases, including overseas.
You think that vampires are involved?
When someone acts to hide something,
their actions will always come off as strange.
I can't shake the feeling that the Hyakko Party and vampires are connected somehow.
There's also that Royal from the other day.
They've left some footprints that we can follow.
I'm sure Kershner will be making his move soon.
You fought a remnant of the Sirius—a mere beast—and now look at you, Agatha.
If, despite this taint, you still pride yourself as a member of our race,
then show me your resolve.
Doctor, it's dinnertime.
Doctor?
Is this his lab?
A bit longer.
Just a bit longer,
Saki.
Foreign newspapers are part of our selection here, though they're a month behind.
Thank you very much.
Please, think nothing of it. Baron Naoe is one of our most valued benefactors.
Thanks for showing me the way.
Ciao!
I think Yuliy's healed enough to return to duty.
Anything else to report?
Not really.
Oh, wait.
What?
Well, I just happened to see the Doctor's papers,
and he's researching some crazy stuff.
From what I could gather...
An artificial heart?
Wow! I had no idea they were this big!
You know, tomatoes used to be ornamental plants.
Really?
People used to think that its red fruit was poisonous, but—
You sure are chatty.
If you see a plant, you can talk like a friggin' lecturer.
Do you hate big brother Yuliy, Philip?
No, it's more like...
Yuliy had a bunch of buddies.
One of those buddies did some bad stuff to my parents.
That makes him annoy me. That's all.
Did big brother Yuliy do something bad, too?
When it comes down to it, I guess he didn't.
Then you can be friends with him!
Jeez.
Want me to play it?
Yeah!
Play it for me, Philip!
So I'm just "Philip," huh.
All right! Let's play a song for the princess!
Saki!
Daddy?
It's done!
Daddy!
It's finished.
I finished it, Saki!
Are you done with work now?
Yes.
Will Mommy be happy?
Yes! I'm sure she will be!
Daddy!
I'm so sorry, Saki.
I'm sorry that I was always too busy.
From now on, everything I do will be for you.
Okay. Okay!
Is that so?
It took him long enough.
So, um, do you have the money you promised me?
I absolutely despise cowardly humans like you.
Lacking even a shred of pride or loyalty, fools fit only to be our livestock.
Please spare—
I looked into all of the researchers the Hyakko Party has killed,
and it seems that all of them have had some of their results stolen.
There were reports of similar cases overseas as well.
It's just as you anticipated.
A biologist who had been researching ways to replace blood...
A college professor who had been trying to develop an iron lung...
Artificial organs.
Research into growing or creating replacements for
organs has been gaining popularity in America and Europe.
I've found out whose car that was.
The one the vampires were using?
Yes. The license plate number matched that of Doctor Hanada's car.
He reported it as stolen when his assistant disappeared.
There's the connection.
What?
You're Mister Willard of V Shipping, right?
It's a pleasure to meet you.
I'm a reporter for True Crime Stories Monthly. Call me Tada.
I apologize, but we're in a rush.
I won't take much of your time.
Would you mind answering just a few questions?
She sure is taking a while to shop.
Let's just make dinner ourselves.
Can you cook, Philip?
You mean "big brother Philip," right?
Japan has good fish, doesn't it?
I'll just whip up some fish and chips and—
What's...
Yuliy.
Buy me twenty seconds!
Yuliy!
The Royal!
I'm sorry, little girl.
I'll be taking your papa for myself.
Though only if my blood accepts him.
Stop!
Daddy!
Daddy! Daddy, don't—
Saki, get away from him!
Philip, stop, he's dying!
Yuliy!
Goddamn it!
Daddy?
Huh?
Who could have expected that a remnant of the Sirius would
hound us all the way to this eastern corner of the world?
I already told you.
You people smell.
So I'll chase you down and kill you until there's not a single one of you left.
I'm completely lost.
Maybe I really would just be a bother if I visit him this late.
Stop! Let go of me, Philip!
We can't do anything!
Oh my, he's turned out quite well.
Saki, run...
What are you staring at?
Saki!
You think you can beat me without paying attention?
Daddy?
Saki!
You mangy Sirius!
Don't make light of me!
You—
D-Disgusting.
Beaten by a Sirius...
Something lower than an animal...
Even if the Ark...
draws you to it now...
it's too...
la—
—te.
The Ark?
Daddy?
Daddy!
Yuliy!
Yuliy.
Brother?
What an unbearable end
I breath out, breath out, breath out, and stop
As I'm fleeing from this cruel world, I fall into a deep sleep
I hide behind the words "I'm doing my best"
But in the end I do nothing but look back
Even when I feel like I've been able to change,
Eventually I realize that the only thing that's changed is the position of the stars
I find myself wondering if everything would feel better if I just broke
Before I fade away while thinking of you,
If I dig out all of my pain then I'll be able to shine like a real star
Will I find a beautiful dream?
This is how we embrace hope
Glowing ash?
With the Ark of Sirius no longer here...
Precious family...
It's possible that he made a blood pact with a vampire.
Dogville.
Live.
The land where our destiny will be made.